Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: Die weisse Dame Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Jul. Weiss Plate Number: J.W.267., undated (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche. Ouverture Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: London (Great Britain): E. Donajowski (E. Donajowski, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: D.7264, undated (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche. Overture Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 15833-88, undated (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche. Overture Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: Boston: W. H. Cundy Plate Number: 242-37(vl 1) 944-27 (vla, cor, drums, undated (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre Plate Number: ANDRE 12851, undated (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 4381, undated (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: Overtura Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Plate Number: 5539, undated (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: The Calif of Bagdad. Overture Uniform Title: Calif of Bagdad. Overture; arr. Publisher information: New York: J. Schott's Plate Number: 254-44, undated (Box 125, Folder 1814)
  - Composer: Borel-Clerc, Ch. Title: La Sorella Uniform Title: Sorella Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 102, Folder 1357)
  - Composer: Borodin, Aleksandr Porfir'evich Title: Ballet Music (Polovetzian Dance) from the Opera Prince Igor, Part 2 Uniform Title: Prince Igor. Polovetsian Dances. Part 2 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 29405, undated (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Composer: Borodin, Aleksandr Porfir'evich Title: Ballet Music (Polovetzian Dances) from the Opera Prince Igor, Part 1 Uniform Title: Prince Igor. Polovetsian Dances. Part 1 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 29403, undated (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Composer: Bortnyans'ky [Bortniansky], Dmytro Stepanovych [Bortnyansky, Dmitry Stepanovich] Title: Ich bete an die Macht der Liebe Uniform Title: Ich bete an die Macht der Liebe, undated (Box 163, Folder 2715)
  - Composer: Bossi, Marco Enrico Title: Hochzeits-Marsch. Marcia Nuziale fur Orgel. Op. 110, No. 4 Uniform Title: Marcia Nuziale fur Orgel. Op. 110, No. 4; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 2373 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Composer: Bossi, Marco Enrico Title: Hochzeits-Marsch. Marcia Nuziale. Op. 110, No. 4 Uniform Title: Wedding March Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 2374 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Composer: Boustet, Ed. Title: Reve Apres le Bal Uniform Title: Reve Apres le Bal Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1593-28, undated (Box 63, Folder 809)
  - Composer: Bovy-Lysberg [Lysberg], Charles Samuel Title: La Fontaine Uniform Title: Fontaine Publisher information: New York: Spear & Dehnhoff Engraver: Cosack & Co., Buffalo, NY, undated (Box 100, Folder 1290)
  - Composer: Bowers, Fred V. Title: Sorrow Uniform Title: Sorrow Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Von Tilzer (Teller, Sons & Dorner, New York [printer]), undated (Box 102, Folder 1354)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: If You Were Lost to Me from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. If You Were Lost to Me Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 106, Folder 1486)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: My House-Boat Beau from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. My House-Boat Beau Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 103, Folder 1376)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: Somewhere in the World from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. Somewhere in the World Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 102, Folder 1366)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: The Little Chauffeur from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. The Little Chauffeur Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 102, Folder 1365)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: The Red Rose. Selection Uniform Title: Red Rose. Selection; arr. Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Composer: Bowman, Euday L. Title: 12th Street Rag Uniform Title: 12th Street Rag; arr. Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., undated (Box 145, Folder 2029)
  - Composer: Bowman, Euday Louis Title: 12th Street Rag Uniform Title: 12th Street Rag Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., undated (Box 159, Folder 2571)
  - Composer: Braga, Gaetano Title: La Serenata Uniform Title: Serenata; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 7529, undated (Box 106, Folder 1493)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Academic Festival Overture, Op. 80 Uniform Title: Akademische Festouverture Publisher information: New York: Hampton Publications Plate Number: HOL-10, undated (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Academic Festival Overture Uniform Title: Akademische Festouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22963-94, undated (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Deutsches Requiem Uniform Title: Deutsches Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 593, undated (Box 89, Folder 1118)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Deutsches Requiem Uniform Title: Deutsches Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 594, undated (Box 89, Folder 1119)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Deutsches Requiem Uniform Title: Deutsches Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 595, undated (Box 89, Folder 1117)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Four Duets for Contralto and Baritone Uniform Title: Four Duets for Contralto and Baritone Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Augener & Co. Plate Number: A & Co. 5063, undated (Box 80, Folder 1033)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Klarinetten Quintett Uniform Title: Quintet, clarinet, violins, viola, violoncello, op. 115, B minor Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 9711, undated (Box 125, Folder 1817)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Liebeslieder Walzer Uniform Title: Liebeslieder Walzer, op. 52 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7025, undated (Box 164, Folder 2781)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodie, op. 53 Plate Number: 10626, undated (Box 169, Folder 2970)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodie, op. 53 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7036, undated (Box 169, Folder 2969)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodies, alto, men's voices, orchestra, op. 53 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7034 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 126, Folder 1824)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodies, alto, men's voices, orchestra, op. 53 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7037 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 126, Folder 1825)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Schicksalslied Uniform Title: Schicksalslied, op. 54 Plate Number: 7178, undated (Box 76, Folder 980)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Schicksalslied Uniform Title: Schicksalslied, op. 54 Plate Number: 7179, undated (Box 76, Folder 981)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Schicksalslied Uniform Title: Schicksalslied Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7177, undated (Box 150, Folder 2182)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Schicksalslied Uniform Title: Schicksalslied Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7179, undated (Box 150, Folder 2183)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Serenade (Nr. 1 D dur) fur grosses Orchester Uniform Title: Serenade no. 1in D major, op. 11 Publisher information: New York: Edwin F. Kalmus, undated (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Serenade Nr. 1, Ddur, Op. 11 Uniform Title: Serenade no. 1in D major, op. 11 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: J.B.8, undated (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Sinfonie Nr. 2 D dur, op. 73 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 2 in D major, op. 73 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.2805/29801, undated (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Symphonie Nr. 2, D dur, Op. 73 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 2 in D major, op. 73 Publisher information: Wiesbaden (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: J. B. 2, undated (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Symphonie Nr. 2, D dur, Op. 73 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 2 in D major, op. 73 Publisher information: Wiesbaden (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.2805, undated (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Zwei ungarishe Tanze Uniform Title: Zwei ungarische Tanze; arr. Plate Number: 7728, undated (Box 175, Folder 3274)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Zwolf Lieder und Romanzen Uniform Title: Zwolf Lieder und Romanzen, op. 44 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 474a. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 101, Folder 1310)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Zwolf Lieder und Romanzen Uniform Title: Zwolf Lieder und Romanzen. Lieder collection Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 474b., undated (Box 87, Folder 1088)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Zwolf Lieder und Romanzen Uniform Title: Zwolf Lieder und Romanzen. Lieder collection Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann Plate Number: 474a. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 87, Folder 1089)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: An die Sonne Uniform Title: An die Sonne Publisher information: Magdeburg (Germany): Otto Wernthal (Oscar Brandstetter, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: O.W. 283 Engraver: Oscar Brandstetter, Leipzig, undated (Box 150, Folder 2194)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Lorelei Uniform Title: Lorelei Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4020 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 164, Folder 2783)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Lorelei Uniform Title: Lorelei Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4021 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 135, Folder 1897)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Lorelei Uniform Title: Lorelei Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4022 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 164, Folder 2784)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Lorelei Uniform Title: Lorelei Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4023 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 135, Folder 1898)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Lorelei Uniform Title: Lorelei Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4024 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 135, Folder 1899)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Mondnacht Uniform Title: Mondnacht Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 3873 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 167, Folder 2879)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Sommernacht Uniform Title: Sommernacht Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 7415 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 171, Folder 3048)
  - Composer: Brambach, C. Jos. Title: Sommernacht Uniform Title: Sommernacht Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Licht & Meyer Plate Number: 33, undated (Box 171, Folder 3049)
  - Composer: Brassin, Louis Title: Nocturne Uniform Title: Nocturne, op. 17 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer (B. Schott's Söhne [printer]) Plate Number: 18103, undated (Box 104, Folder 1413)
  - Composer: Braune, Otto Title: Gott in der Natur Uniform Title: Gott in der Natur, undated (Box 138, Folder 1934)
  - Composer: Brenner, Friedrich Title: Zwei geistliche und zehn weltliche Gesange Uniform Title: Gesange, voice, piano Publisher information: Dorpat (Estonia): A. Jessen (E. Jul. Pickenhahn, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 1 Engraver: E. Jul. Pickenhahn, Leipzig, undated (Box 128, Folder 1868)
  - Composer: Breu, Simon Title: Ewig liebe Heimat Uniform Title: Ewig liebe Heimat Publisher information: Wurzburg (Germany): Universitats-Druckerei (H. Sturtz), undated (Box 157, Folder 2477)
  - Composer: Breu, Simon Title: Forsters Sturmlied Uniform Title: Forsters Sturmlied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9870, undated (Box 158, Folder 2518)
  - Composer: Breu, Simon Title: Fruhling am Rhein Uniform Title: Fruhling am Rhein Publisher information: Coburg (Germany): Conrad Glaser (Oscar Brandstetter, vorm. F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: C. G. 499 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated (Box 157, Folder 2487)
  - Composer: Breu, Simon Title: Lied in der Fremde Uniform Title: Lied in der Fremde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9311 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 149, Folder 2167)
  - Composer: Briegel, George F., arr. Title: Hymn of Thanksgiving Uniform Title: Hymn of Thanksgiving; arr., undated (Box 107, Folder 1524)
  - Composer: Briegel, George F., arr. Title: Seraphic Song Uniform Title: Seraphic Song; arr., undated (Box 107, Folder 1530)
  - Composer: Broll, Heinrich Title: Die Muhle im Tale Uniform Title: Muhle im Tale Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Conrad Glaser, Musikalien- und Theaterverlag (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: C. 5915 G. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 153, Folder 2316)
  - Composer: Broustet, Edward Title: Yaya. Danse Creole Uniform Title: Yaya. Dance Creole Publisher information: Nice (France): Paul Decourelle Plate Number: P.D.327, undated (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Composer: Brown, Lew, Wladimir A. Timm and Jaromir Vejvoda Title: Beer Barrel Polka Uniform Title: Beer Barrel Polka Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., undated (Box 125, Folder 1822)
  - Composer: Brown, Lew, Wladimir A. Timm, and Jaromir Vejvoda Title: Beer Barrel Polka Uniform Title: Beer Barrel Polka Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., undated (Box 159, Folder 2549)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Achilleus Uniform Title: Achilleus Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 8544, undated (Box 83, Folder 1062)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Achilleus Uniform Title: Achilleus Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 8545, undated (Box 80, Folder 1035)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Arminius Uniform Title: Arminius (Germany) (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7801, undated (Box 88, Folder 1112)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Arminius Uniform Title: Arminius Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7799 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 86, Folder 1079)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Concert fur die Violine Uniform Title: Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 26, G minor Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 5801 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 88, Folder 1110)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Concert fur die Violine Uniform Title: Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 26, G minor Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 5802 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 88, Folder 1111)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Das Feuerkreuz Uniform Title: Feuerkreuz Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9204 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 143, Folder 1984)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Das Lied von der Glocke Uniform Title: Lied von der Glocke (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 8087, undated (Box 141, Folder 1963)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Das Lied von der Glocke Uniform Title: Lied von der Glocke (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 8089, undated (Box 165, Folder 2793)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Der 23te Psalm Uniform Title: 23. Psalm Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 10704 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 151, Folder 2239)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Einleitung zu der Oper Loreley Uniform Title: Loreley. Overture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C.F.W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (R. Linnemann) Plate Number: 5350 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Einleitung zu der Oper Loreley Uniform Title: Loreley. Overture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C.F.W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (R. Linnemann) Plate Number: 5351 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Einleitung zu der Oper Loreley Uniform Title: Loreley. Overture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.2024 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Uniform Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 2125 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 141, Folder 1973)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Uniform Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 2129 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 141, Folder 1974)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Uniform Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 2130, undated (Box 141, Folder 1972)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Uniform Title: Frithjof auf seines Vaters Grabhugel Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.2128, undated (Box 158, Folder 2516)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht. Weihnachtshymne Uniform Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 9797 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 142, Folder 1978)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht. Weihnachtshymne Uniform Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 9798 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 142, Folder 1977)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht. Weihnachtshymne Uniform Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 9799 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 154, Folder 2352)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht. Weihnachtshymne Uniform Title: Gruss an die heilige Nacht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 9800 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 154, Folder 2353)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Kol Nidrei (Hebrew Melodies) Uniform Title: Kol Nidrei; arr. Publisher information: New York: Ross Jungnickel Plate Number: 24-42, undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Kriegsgesang aus Des Epimenides Erwachen von Goethe Uniform Title: Epimenides Erwachen. Kriegsgesang Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 10708, undated (Box 158, Folder 2514)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Kriegsgesang aus Des Epimenides Erwachen von Goethe Uniform Title: Epimenides Erwachen. Kriegsgesang Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 10709, undated (Box 121, Folder 1733)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Normannenzug Uniform Title: Normannenzug Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 12089, undated (Box 168, Folder 2910)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Normannenzug Uniform Title: Normannenzug Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Ch.B.58., undated (Box 168, Folder 2909)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Odysseus. Scenen Uniform Title: Odysseus. Selection Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7208 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 168, Folder 2929)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Odysseus. Vorspiel Uniform Title: Odysseus. Vorspiel Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7268 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 114, Folder 1629)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Odysseus. Vorspiel Uniform Title: Odysseus. Vorspiel Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7270 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 114, Folder 1628)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Romischer Triumphgesang Uniform Title: Romischer Triumphgesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 5381 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 169, Folder 2973)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Romischer Triumphgesang Uniform Title: Romischer Triumphgesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 1771, undated (Box 169, Folder 2974)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Scenen aus der Frithjof-Sage Uniform Title: Frithjof-Sage. Selections Plate Number: 5903, undated (Box 157, Folder 2497)
  - Composer: Bruch, Max Title: Scenen aus der Frithjof-Sage Uniform Title: Frithjof-Sage. Selections Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 1896. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 136, Folder 1913)